Ronald Salinas-Roy

Ottawa, ON | K1B 5A5 | 613-447-1002

ronaldsalinasroy.github.io/ | ronaldsalinasroy@outlook.com | www.linkedin.com/in/ronald-salinas-roy/

ABOUT ME

I am a hard worker who commits to ensuring tasks are completed, with meticulous attention to methods and details. I am patient with myself and those around me, providing a friendly and empathetic experience. My hopes are to find opportunities that offer learning experiences, through failures and successes, to hone my skills and personal growth.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science Minor in Greek and Roman Studies

• Carleton University, Ottawa, ON

September 2017-June 2022

SKILLS

Communication Skills

- Experience with Microsoft and Google programs to produce documents, presentations, and spreadsheets
- Customer service with a positive attitude and willingness to help
- Fluent in English: oral, written, and reading

Technical Skills

- Programming Languages: C, C#, C++, Java, JavaScript, Python, Scheme, Swift, Visual Basic
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Operating Systems: Linux, MacOS, Windows
- Developer Tools: Android Studio, Eclipse, IntelliJ, VirtualBox, Visual Studio, Webots, Xcode

WORK EXPERIENCE

Produce Clerk

January 2024-Present

Metro Inc., Ottawa, ON

- Managing production and ensuring shelves are maintained and stocked
- Training employees with the scope of job expectations and responsibilities
- Providing customer service in fulfilling orders and answering questions
- Flexibility in filling in for other departments like bakery and grocery
- Cleaning department tools and surfaces and dealing with quality control of products

Bakery Clerk

September 2022-September 2023

Metro Inc., Ottawa, ON

- Providing customer service in taking orders, cake writing, and answering questions
- Managing production and ensuring shelves are maintained and stocked
- Training employees with the scope of job expectations and responsibilities